<resources>
    <string name="app_name">User Manual</string>
    <string name="power_on_details">
        • Turn on the solar-powered power supply to activate the hardware components.
    </string>
    <string name="servo_motor_control_details">
        • Use the Logitech Extreme 3D Pro joystick to control the collective movement of the helicopter rotor assembly.\n\n
        • Push the joystick forward, backward, left, or right to maneuver the rotor assembly accordingly.
    </string>
    <string name="stepper_motor_speed_control_details">
        • Rotate the potentiometer knob to adjust the speed of the stepper motor.\n\n
        • Turn the knob clockwise to increase speed and counterclockwise to decrease speed.
    </string>
    <string name="hardware_not_responding_details">
        • Ensure that the power supply is turned on and properly connected.\n\n
        • Check the connections between the servo motors, stepper motor, and Arduino Mega controller.\n\n
        • Verify that the Arduino Mega is powered on and functioning correctly.\n\n
        • If hardware components are damaged or malfunctioning, spare parts for each component will be provided for replacement.
    </string>
    <string name="stepper_motor_speed_issues">
        • If the stepper motor speed is not adjusting as expected:\n\n
          \t\t -Check the wiring connections between the potentiometer and the Arduino Mega.\n\n
        • Ensure that the potentiometer is functioning properly by testing with a multimeter.\n\n
        • Adjust the code in the Arduino Mega to calibrate the speed control.\n\n
        • If the stepper motor itself is faulty, spare stepper motor components will be provided for replacement.
    </string>

    <string name="servo_motors_not_moving_details">
        If the servo motors are not responding to joystick inputs:\n\n
        \t\t • Confirm that the Logitech Extreme 3D Pro joystick is connected securely to the Arduino Mega.\n\n
        \t\t • Check the code in the Arduino Mega to ensure proper mapping of joystick inputs to servo motor control.\n\n
        \t\t • Verify that the servo motors are receiving power and are connected correctly to the Arduino Mega.\n\n
        \t\t • If the servo motors are damaged or malfunctioning, spare servo motor components will be provided for replacement.
    </string>

    <string name="arduino_mega_reset">
        If troubleshooting does not resolve the issue, try resetting the Arduino Mega:\n\n
        \t\t • Locate the reset button on the Arduino Mega board.\n\n
        \t\t • Press the reset button to restart the microcontroller and reset any potential software issues.\n\n
        \t\t • After resetting, check if the hardware components respond as expected.\n\n
        \t\t • If the Arduino Mega itself is damaged or malfunctioning, spare Arduino Mega boards will be provided for replacement.
    </string>
    <string name="further_assistance_details">
        If issues persist, refer to the project documentation or seek assistance from a knowledgeable individual with experience in Arduino programming and hardware troubleshooting. Spare parts will be available upon request for replacement of damaged or malfunctioning components.\n\n

    </string>

    <string name="components">
        • 4 MG996R Servo Motors: Responsible for collective movement.\n\n
        • NEMA 17 Stepper Motor: Controls the throttle.\n\n
        • Arduino Mega: Main controller board for the system.\n\n
        • Potentiometer: Used to control the speed of the stepper motor.\n\n
        • Logitech Extreme 3D Pro: Controller for collective movements.\n\n
        • Solar-Powered Power Supply: Provides power to the entire system.\n\n
        • 3D Printed Parts: Includes rotor blades, swashplates, and other structural components.
    </string>

    <string name="assembly">
        \t\t • Connect the MG996R servo motors to their designated positions on the rotor assembly.\n\n
        \t\t • Attach the NEMA 17 stepper motor to its mounting point.\n\n
        \t\t • Connect the potentiometer to the stepper motor driver.\n\n
        \t\t• Mount the Logitech Extreme 3D Pro controller securely.\n\n
        \t\t• Assemble the 3D printed parts as per the provided diagram.
    </string>
    <string name="wiring_and_connections">
        \t\t• Connect the servo motors to the designated pins on the Arduino Mega.\n\n
        \t\t• Wire the stepper motor to its driver, and then connect the driver to the Arduino Mega.\n\n
        \t\t• Attach the potentiometer to the appropriate analog input on the Arduino Mega.\n\n
        \t\t• Connect the Logitech Extreme 3D Pro to the Arduino Mega via the USB port.\n\n
        \t\t• Ensure all connections are secure and tidy
    </string>

    <string name="power_supply">
        \t\t• Connect the solar-powered power supply to the Arduino Mega and other components.\n\n
        \t\t• Ensure the power supply is placed in an area with sufficient sunlight.

    </string>
    <string name="initial_power_on">
        \t\t• Turn on the solar-powered power supply.\n\n
        \t\t• Verify that all components receive power and the Arduino Mega lights up.
    </string>

    <string name="turning_on_the_system">
        \t\t• Switch on the solar-powered power supply.\n\n
        \t\t• Ensure all components are powered up correctly
    </string>
    <string name="controlling_the_rotor_assembly">
        \t\t• Use the Logitech Extreme 3D Pro controller to manage collective movements.\n\n
        \t\t• Push the stick forward/backward to control pitch.\n\n
        \t\t• Adjust the potentiometer to control the speed of the NEMA 17 stepper motor
    </string>
    <string name="calibration_and_testing">
        \t\t• Perform initial tests by moving the controller to ensure the servo motors respond correctly.\n\n
        \t\t• Adjust the potentiometer and verify the stepper motor’s speed changes accordingly.
    </string>
    <string name="safety_precautions">
        \t\t• Always turn off the power supply before making any adjustments.\n\n
        \t\t• Handle all components with care to avoid damage.\n\n
        \t\t• Ensure the rotor assembly is placed in a safe, stable area during operation.
    </string>
    <string name="power_issues">
        \t• Solution:\n\n
        \t\t\t\t1. Check if the solar-powered power supply is properly connected and exposed to sufficient sunlight.\n\n
        \t\t\t\t2. Ensure all connections from the power supply to the hardware are secure.\n\n
        \t\t\t\t3. Verify that the power switch is turned on.

    </string>

    <string name="servo_motors_issue">
        \t• Solution:\n\n
        \t\t\t\t1. Ensure that the Logitech Extreme 3D Pro controller is properly connected to the Arduino Mega.\n\n
        \t\t\t\t2. Check the connections between the servo motors and the Arduino Mega.\n\n
        \t\t\t\t3. Press the reset button on the Arduino Mega to restart the system.
    </string>

    <string name="stepper_motor_issues">
        \t• Solution:\n\n
        \t\t\t\t1. Check the connection between the stepper motor and the potentiometer.\n\n
        \t\t\t\t2. Ensure the stepper motor driver is properly connected to the Arduino Mega.\n\n
        \t\t\t\t3. Press the reset button on the Arduino Mega to restart the system.
    </string>
    <string name="connetivity_issues">
        \t• Solution:\n\n
        \t\t\t\t1. Ensure all cables and connections between components (Arduino Mega, servo motors, stepper motor, potentiometer, and Logitech controller) are secure.\n\n
        \t\t\t\t2. Check for any loose wires or broken connections.\n\n
        \t\t\t\t3. Reset the Arduino Mega to re-establish connections.

    </string>
    <string name="movement_issues">
        \t• Solution:\n\n
        \t\t\t\t1. Check the alignment and secure mounting of all mechanical parts.\n\n
        \t\t\t\t2. Ensure the servo motors and stepper motor are properly calibrated and receiving correct signals from the Arduino.
    </string>
    <string name="general_maintenance">
        \t• Solution:\n\n
        \t\t\t\t1. Regularly check all connections and secure any loose wires or components.\n\n
        \t\t\t\t2. Clean the hardware components to prevent dust and debris buildup.\n\n
        \t\t\t\t3. Lubricate moving parts to ensure smooth operation.
    </string>
    <string name="software_issues">
        \t• Solution:\n\n
        \t\t\t\t1. Ensure the latest version of the software is installed.\n\n
        \t\t\t\t2. Restart the software and, if necessary, reinstall it.
    </string>
    <string name="emergency_shutdown">
        \t• Solution:\n\n
        \t\t\t\t1. Turn off the power supply immediately.\n\n
        \t\t\t\t2. Disconnect the solar power supply from the hardware.\n\n
        \t\t\t\t3. Ensure all components have powered down safely before performing any checks or repairs.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="MG996R_servo_motors">
        \t\t• Description: The MG996R is a high-torque servo motor commonly used in robotics and mechanical applications.\n\n
        \t\t• Function: Responsible for controlling the collective movement of the helicopter rotor blades, allowing for precise adjustments in pitch.\n\n
        \t\t• Key Features:\n\n
        \t\t\t\t• High torque output\n\n
        \t\t\t\t• Metal gears for durability\n\n
        \t\t\t\t• Wide operating voltage range\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="NEMA_17_Stepper_Motor">
        \t\t• Description: A type of stepper motor widely used in 3D printers, CNC machines, and other applications requiring precise control of movement.\n\n
        \t\t• Function: Controls the throttle of the rotor assembly, regulating the speed of the rotor blades.\n\n
        \t\t• Key Features:\n\n
        \t\t\t\t• High precision and control\n\n
        \t\t\t\t• Robust and reliable performance\n\n
        \t\t\t\t• Multiple step angles for detailed movement

    </string>
    <string name="Arduino_Mega">
        \t\t• Description: A microcontroller board based on the ATmega2560, offering extensive I/O capabilities.\n\n
        \t\t• Function: Acts as the main controller for the system, processing inputs from the potentiometer and the Logitech controller to manage the servo and stepper motors.\n\n
        \t\t• Key Features:\n\n
        \t\t\t\t• 54 digital I/O pins\n\n
        \t\t\t\t• 16 analog inputs\n\n
        \t\t\t\t• Large memory capacity for complex programs

    </string>

    <string name="potentiometer">
        \t\t• Description: An adjustable resistor used to control electrical devices.\n\n
        \t\t• Function: Used to adjust the speed of the NEMA 17 stepper motor by varying resistance and providing input to the Arduino Mega.\n\n
        \t\t• Key Features:\n\n
        \t\t\t\t• Smooth rotation for precise control\n\n
        \t\t\t\t• Durable construction\n\n
        \t\t\t\t• Easy to integrate with microcontrollers
    </string>
    <string name="Logitech_Extreme_3D_Pro">
        \t\t• Description: A joystick controller designed for gaming and simulation applications.\n\n
        \t\t• Function: Provides input for controlling the collective movements of the rotor blades, allowing users to simulate real-life helicopter maneuvers.\n\n
        \t\t• Key Features:\n\n
        \t\t\t\t• 12 programmable buttons\n\n
        \t\t\t\t• High-precision joystick\n\n
        \t\t\t\t• Comfortable and ergonomic design
    </string>
    <string name="Solar_Powered_Power_Supply">
        \t\t• Description: A power supply unit that converts solar energy into electrical energy to power the system.\n\n
        \t\t• Function: Provides renewable and sustainable power to the entire rotor assembly model.\n\n
        \t\t• Key Features:\n\n
        \t\t\t\t• Environmentally friendly energy source\n\n
        \t\t\t\t• Reliable power output\n\n
        \t\t\t\t• Reduces dependency on traditional power sources
    </string>
    <string name="Printed_Parts">
    \t\t• <b> Swashplate </b>\n\n
    \t\t\t\t• Description: A critical part of the rotor system that connects to the rotor blades.\n\n
    \t\t\t\t• Function: Allows for the transfer of control inputs from the servos to the rotor blades.\n\n\n
        \t\t• <b>Lower Swashplate</b>\n\n
    \t\t\t\t• Description: Works in conjunction with the upper swashplate to control the blade pitch.\n\n
    \t\t\t\t• Function: Ensures coordinated movement of the rotor blades.\n\n\n
    \t\t• <b>Blade Grip</b>\n\n
    \t\t\t\t• Description: Holds the rotor blades securely.\n\n
    \t\t\t\t• Function: Ensures stable attachment of the rotor blades to the assembly.\n\n\n
        \t\t• <b>Rotor Blades</b>\n\n
    \t\t\t\t• Description: Main aerodynamic surfaces that generate lift.\n\n
    \t\t\t\t• Function: Provide the necessary lift and thrust for the rotor assembly.\n\n\n
        \t\t• <b>Ball Joint</b>\n\n
    \t\t\t\t• Description: A spherical bearing allowing for multi-directional movement.\n\n
    \t\t\t\t• Function: Facilitates smooth movement of control surfaces.\n\n\n
        \t\t• <b>Rotor Mast</b>\n\n
    \t\t\t\t• Description: The central shaft of the rotor system.\n\n
    \t\t\t\t• Function: Supports the rotor blades and transmits rotational force.\n\n\n
    \t\t•     <b>Base</b>\n\n
    \t\t\t\t• Description: The foundation of the rotor assembly model.\n\n
    \t\t\t\t• Function: Provides stability and support to the entire structure.\n\n\n
        \t\t• <b>Servo Base</b>\n\n
    \t\t\t\t• Description: Mounting platform for servo motors.\n\n
    \t\t\t\t• Function: Secures the servos in place for optimal performance.
    </string>
</resources>